Contact

3 Stanborough Mews keagangonsalves_18@hotmail. com

www.linkedin.com/in/keagangonsalves-b9233686 (LinkedIn) keags14.github.io/ (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Agile Methodologies

Git

Test Automation

Languages

Arabic

English

Konkani

Hindi

French

Certifications

Android Development Essential Training: App Architecture with Kotlin

Certified Tester Foundation Level (CTFL)

Android Development Essential Training: Manage Data with Kotlin

Android Development Essential Training: Distributing Apps with Java

Developing CI/CD Solutions with Azure DevOps

Keagan Gonsalves

Test Automation Engineer @ Tandem Bank | MSc. Software Engineering | ISTQB CTFL Certified | Driving Quality & Efficiency through Automated Testing

United Kingdom

Summary

I am an experienced QA automation engineer based in the United Kingdom with a diverse skill set encompassing MySQL, Java, and Behaviour-Driven Development (BDD). My proficiency extends to Kotlin, C#, Cucumber, and QTP, allowing me to excel in test automation framework development and implementation. I hold a Master of Science (M.Sc.) in Software Engineering from the University of Hertfordshire, underlining my commitment to continuous learning and professional growth.

Experience

Tandem Bank
Test Automation Engineer
October 2023 - Present (1 year 1 month)
London, England, United Kingdom

Sparta Global

Junior C# SDET and Developer Consultant June 2021 - May 2023 (2 years)

London, England, United Kingdom

- Designed and implemented automation test scripts for software applications using Java and Selenium WebDriver.
- Developed and maintained a test automation framework using Cucumber and QTP.
- Conducted regression testing and identified and reported software defects.
- Collaborated with developers and business analysts to ensure testing requirements were met.
- Tested and verified software functionality and performance using MySQL and Java.
- Created and executed test cases and reported software defects.
- Developed and maintained testing documentation and reported testing progress to management.

- Collaborated with developers to troubleshoot and resolve issues.
- Performed cross browser testing with different operating systems using browser stack.
- Integration of CI/CD with Git

Contracted Companies: All Saints, Sky.

Qing Co., Ltd Junior Software Developer August 2018 - February 2019 (7 months)

- Team briefings
- Implementation using Java, jQuery, HTML, CSS and MySQL
- MVC architectures design and system testing.
- Implementation using Waterfall life cycle.

Actus Software

Technical Support Analyst November 2016 - October 2017 (1 year)

Redbourn, England, United Kingdom

- Customer Support
- Setting up new clients and upskilling of new users
- UAT (User Acceptance Testing) and bug fixes
- Manage and Update the company website
- Document and provide support for new system releases
- Provide weekly and monthly reports

Education

University of Hertfordshire

Master's Degree, Computer Software Engineering (2019 - 2020)

University of Hertfordshire

Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.), Computer Science · (2013 - 2016)

CSK

AISSCE, Computer Science · (January 2009 - December 2010)